Valerie's about to discover how far a girl has to go to find Mr. Right.
Earth Girls Are Easy is a comedy, science fiction,
music film directed by Julien Temple.
In this musical comedy, Valerie is dealing with her philandering fiancé, Ted, when she finds
that a trio of aliens have crashed their spaceship into her swimming pool.
Once the furry beings are shaved at her girlfriend's salon, the
women discover three handsome men underneath.
After absorbing the native culture via television, the spacemen are
ready to hit the dating scene in 1980s Los Angeles.
Valerie Gail, played by Geena Davis.
Mac, played by Jeff Goldblum.
Wiploc, played by Jim Carrey.
Zeebo, played by Damon Wayans.
Candy Pink, played by Julie Brown.
Woody, played by Michael McKean.
Earth Girls Are Easy is a 1988 American science fiction musical romantic comedy film
that was produced by Tony Garnett, Duncan Henderson, and Terrence E.
McNally and was directed by Julien Temple.
The film stars Geena Davis, Jeff Goldblum, Jim Carrey, Damon
Wayans, Julie Brown, Charles Rocket and Michael McKean.
The plot is based on the song "Earth Girls Are Easy"
from Brown's 1984 EP Goddess in Progress.
The film explores themes of spacecraft, dancing, dreams, police, musical.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.